[
    {
        "front": "Ikimas",
        "back": "To go",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Kimas",
        "back": "to come",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Kaerimas",
        "back": "To return",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Mimas",
        "back": "To see",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Kikimas",
        "back": "To hear",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Shimas",
        "back": "To do",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Tabemas",
        "back": "To eat",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Nomimas",
        "back": "To drink",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Yomimas",
        "back": "To read",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Nihon",
        "back": "Japan",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Kankoku",
        "back": "Korea",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Chūgoku",
        "back": "China",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Indo",
        "back": "India",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Kuni",
        "back": "Country",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Uchi",
        "back": "Home",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Ie",
        "back": "House",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Suki",
        "back": "Like         <adj.>",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Kirai",
        "back": "Dislike",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Osake",
        "back": "Wine, whisky, alcohol",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Shokuji",
        "back": "Food (Meal)",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Gohan",
        "back": "Food",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Sushi",
        "back": "Raw fish rolled in rice",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Sakana",
        "back": "Fish",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Niku",
        "back": "Meat",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Gyūniku",
        "back": "Beef",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Butaniku",
        "back": "Pork",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Toriniku",
        "back": "Chicken",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Tori",
        "back": "Chicken",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Tamago",
        "back": "Eggs",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Gyūnyu",
        "back": "Milk",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Shigoto",
        "back": "Work, job",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Eiga",
        "back": "Film, movie",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Eigakan",
        "back": "Movie theater",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Ongaku",
        "back": "Music",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Shimbun",
        "back": "Newspaper",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Hon",
        "back": "Book",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Terebi",
        "back": "TV",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Hanabi",
        "back": "Fire crackers show",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Hanami",
        "back": "Cherry flower",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Gakkō",
        "back": "School",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Kaisha",
        "back": "Company, office",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Ocha",
        "back": "Tea",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Mizu",
        "back": "Water",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Korekara",
        "back": "From now on",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Sorekara",
        "back": "After that",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Mashō",
        "back": "‘let’s’",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "to issho ni",
        "back": "‘with’",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Benkyō",
        "back": "Study",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Hirugohan",
        "back": "Lunch",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Asa",
        "back": "Morning",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Kesa",
        "back": "Today Morning",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Yoru",
        "back": "Night",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Raishū",
        "back": "Next week",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Mainichi",
        "back": "Daily",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Maiban",
        "back": "Every evening",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Sakka",
        "back": "Soccer",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Nara",
        "back": "(Place)",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "Uriba",
        "back": "~department",
        "chapter": 6
    },
    {
        "front": "chika ikkai",
        "back": "First basement floor",
        "chapter": 6
    }
]